{
    "items": [
        {
            "Question": "HTML stands for -",
            "Choices": [
                "HighText Machine Language",
                "HyperText and links Markup Language",
                "HyperText Markup Language",
                "None of these"
            ],
            "Answer": "HyperText Markup Language",
            "Selected":""
        },
        {
            "Question": "The correct sequence of HTML tags for starting a webpage is - ",
            "Choices": [
                "Head, Title, HTML, body",
                "HTML, Body, Title, Head",
                "HTML, Head, Title, Body",
                "HTML, Head, Body, Title"
            ],
            "Answer": "HTML, Head, Title, Body",
            "Selected":""
        },
        {
            "Question": "Which of the following element is responsible for making the text bold in HTML?",
            "Choices": [
                "<pre>",
                "<a>",
                "<b>",
                "<br>"

            ],
            "Answer": "<b>",
            "Selected":""
        },
        {
            "Question": "Which of the following tag is used for inserting the largest heading in HTML?",
            "Choices": [
                "<h3>",
                "<h1>",
                "<h5>",
                "<h6>"
            ],
            "Answer": "<h1>",
            "Selected":""
        },
        {
            "Question": "Which of the following tag is used to insert a line-break in HTML?",
            "Choices": [
                "<br>",
                "<a>",
                "<pre>",
                "<b>"
            ],
            "Answer": "<br>",
            "Selected":""
        },
        {
            "Question": "How to create an unordered list (a list with the list items in bullets) in HTML?",
            "Choices": [
                "<ul>",
                "<ol>",
                "<li>",
                "<i>"
            ],
            "Answer": "<ul>",
            "Selected":""
        },
        {
            "Question": "Which of the following attribute is used to provide a unique name to an element?",
            "Choices": [
                    
                "class",
                "id",
                "type",
                "None of the above"

            ],
            "Answer": "id",
            "Selected":""
        },
        {
            "Question": "How to create an ordered list (a list with the list items in numbers) in HTML?",
            "Choices": [
                
                    "<ul>",
                    "<ol>",
                    "<li>",
                    "<i>"
 
            ],
            "Answer": "<ol>",
            "Selected":""
        },
        {
            "Question": "Which of the following element is responsible for making the text italic in HTML?",
            "Choices": [
                "<i>",
                "<italic>",
                "<it>",
                "<pre>"
            ],
            "Answer": "<i>",
            "Selected":""
        },
        {
            "Question": "The <hr> tag in HTML is used for -",
            "Choices": [
                "new line",
                "vertical ruler",
                "new paragraph",
                "horizontal ruler"
            ],
            "Answer": "horizontal ruler",
            "Selected":""
        },
        {
            "Question": "<input> is -",
            "Choices": [
                "a format tag.",
                "an empty tag.",
                "All of the above",
                "None of the above"
            ],
            "Answer": "an empty tag.",
            "Selected":""
        },
        {
            "Question": "Which of the following tag is used to make the underlined text?",
            "Choices": [
                "<i>",
                "<ul>",
                "<u>",
                "<pre>"
            ],
            "Answer": "<u>",
            "Selected":""
        },
        {
            "Question": "Which of the following tag is used to define options in a drop-down selection list?",
            "Choices": [
                "<select>",
                "<list>",
                "<dropdown>",
                "<option>"
            ],
            "Answer": "<option>",
            "Selected":""
        },
        {
            "Question": "HTML tags are enclosed in-",
            "Choices": [
                "# and #",
                "{ and }",
                "! and ?",
                "< and >"
            ],
            "Answer": "< and >",
            "Selected":""
        },
        {
            "Question": "Which of the following tag is used to add rows in the table?",
            "Choices": [
                "<td> and </td>",
                "<th> and </th>",
                "<tr> and </tr>",
                "None of the above"
            ],
            "Answer": "<tr> and </tr>",
            "Selected":""
        }
    ]
}